League of Women Voters mss., 1913-2014 LMC 2371
Lilly Library
- Administrative Files
  - Hazardous Waste Exchange (Box 27)
  - SW/HW - HW, PCB, Geril (Box 27)
  - Hazardous Waste General (Box 27)
  - Westinghouse, EPA and Misc. (Box 27)
  - Units PCB, 1987-1988 (Box 27)
  - Local PCBs (Box 28)
  - Bylaws - CSBAs (Box 28)
  - Citizens' School Board Assembly, 1970-1972 (Box 28)
  - Solid Waste (Box 28)
  - Juvenile Treatment Center (Box 28)
  - Vi Simpson - Taxation 101, graphs, notes (Box 28)
  - Kindergarten (Box 28)
  - Minutes, 2004-2005 (Box 28)
  - Newsletters (Box 28)
  - Essay Contest (Box 28)
  - Nominating Committee of the Citizens' School (Box 28)
  - 1972 Nominating Committee (Box 28)
  - National Voter (Box 29)
  - Voters Rights (Box 29)
  - National Program (Box 29)
  - Congress (Box 29)
  - China-U.N. (Box 29)
  - Aid and Trade (Box 29)
  - State Convention (Box 29)
  - State (Box 29)
  - Board List (Box 29)
  - Board Reports (Box 29)
  - Bylaws (Box 29)
  - Convention 1974 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence (Box 29)
  - Nominating Committee (Box 29)
  - Public Relations (Box 29)
  - Publications (Box 29)
  - Voters (Box 29)
  - State Program (Box 29)
  - Board Reports (Box 29)
  - Government Election Laws (Box 30)
  - Government Voters Rights (Box 30)
  - Government Debates (Box 30)
  - Government Miscellaneous Materials (Box 30)
  - International Relations - Arms Control (Box 30)
  - International Relations - Foreign Policy (Box 30)
  - International Relations - National Security (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Clean Air (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Energy (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Forest (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Land Uses (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Safe Drinking Water, 1986-1988 (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Waste Management, Hazardous Waste (Box 30)
  - Natural Resources - Waste Management, Municipal Solid Waste (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Women's Finances (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Women and Work (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Literacy, 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Access to Education (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Equal Rights, 1982-1984 (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Meeting Basic Human Needs, Study Consensus, 1986-1988 (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Health Care (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - General Assistance (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Block Grants and Social Needs (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Pre-Trial Release (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Urban Crises, 1979 (Box 30)
  - Social Policy - Transportation (Box 30)
  - Program - Recorders Forms (Box 30)
  - Program - Program Planning of General Use (Box 30)
  - Program - Possible Programs (Box 30)
  - Program - Program Planning and Bylaws (Box 30)
  - Program - Program Planning (Box 30)
  - Program - Programs or Reports (Box 30)
  - Contributions (Box 31)
  - Financial, 1989-2005 (Box 31)
  - Clippings (Box 31)
  - Plaque, March 1991 (Box 31)
  - Economic Conversion Info (Box 31)
  - Long-Term Health Care (Box 31)
  - Health-Care Study (Box 31)
  - Low Cost Housing (Box 31)
  - How Bill Becomes Law (Box 31)
  - Take Back the System (Box 31)
  - Convention '92 (Box 32)
  - League Profile (Box 32)
  - 75th Anniversary Convention (Box 32)
  - Strategic Plan Report (Box 32)
  - Balanced Budget (Box 32)
  - Local Government (Box 32)
  - Juvenile Justice (Box 32)
  - Children at Risk (Box 32)
  - Juvenile Justice (Box 32)
  - Children at Risk (Box 32)
  - Juvenile Justice (Box 32)
  - Domestic Violence (Box 32)
  - Crossroads (Box 32)
  - Publications (Box 32)
  - Congressional Debates (Box 32)
  - Location Security (Box 32)
  - Advisory CMT (Box 32)
  - Publicity (Box 32)
  - Format (Box 32)
  - Legislature (Box 32)
  - Headstart (Box 32)
  - Legislative Activities (Box 32)
  - Voters' Service (Box 32)
  - Gun Control (Box 32)
  - Debate (?) 1994 Congressional (Box 32)
  - Observers (Box 32)
  - Observers' Corp. (Box 32)
  - Bloomington Feminist Chorus (Box 32)
  - Public Relations (Box 32)
  - SB Debate (Box 32)
  - Leadership (Box 32)
  - Med Sci.... (Box 32)
  - Space (Box 32)
  - Welfare Reform (Box 33)
  - State BD Reports (Box 33)
  - Jail Task Force (Box 33)
  - National BD Summaries (Box 33)
  - Federal Deficit (Box 33)
  - House Bill 1286 (Box 33)
  - Board Meeting (Box 33)
  - File (Box 33)
  - League (Box 33)
  - Publications (Box 33)
  - Bd. Meeting (Box 33)
  - Annual Meeting (Box 34)
  - Agenda - Board Minutes (Box 34)
  - Reports (Box 34)
  - Board Training (Box 34)
  - Budget (Box 34)
  - By-Laws (Box 34)
  - Calendar (Box 34)
  - Correspondence - Local Archives (Box 34)
  - Correspondence - Organizations (Box 34)
  - National Security (Box 34)
  - Highlights (Box 34)
  - Insurance - Liability (Box 34)
  - League Letter (Box 34)
  - League Letters - Other Leagues (Box 34)
  - Mailing Information (Box 34)
  - Membership (Box 34)
  - Monroe County Fair (Box 34)
  - Membership Renewal Letters (Box 34)
  - Officials List (Box 34)
  - Portfolio Inventory List Forms (Box 34)
  - Program - Local (Box 34)
  - Program Planning Background (Box 34)
  - Publications (Box 34)
  - Publications - Flyers (Box 34)
  - Statements and Letters to the Editor (Box 34)
  - Stationary (Box 34)
  - Tax Law Information (Box 34)
  - Treasurer (Box 34)
  - Telephone Tree (Box 34)
  - Who Does What? (Box 34)
  - By-Laws (Box 34)
  - Coalition Policy (Box 34)
  - Calendar (Box 34)
  - League Letters (Box 34)
  - History (Box 34)
  - Officers (Box 34)
  - PMP (Box 34)
  - Program (Box 34)
  - State Board Reports (Box 34)
  - Ad Hoc Committee - Grassroots (Box 34)
  - By-Laws (Box 34)
  - State Convention (Box 34)
  - State Council (Box 34)
  - Brochures (Box 34)
  - Voter (Box 34)
  - Convention (Box 34)
  - Council (Box 34)
  - Corresponence (Box 34)
  - Memos (Box 34)
  - President's Packet (Box 34)
  - Program: "Impact on Issues" (Box 34)
  - Prospectus (Box 34)
  - Report from the Hill (Box 34)
  - Roster (Box 34)
  - Post Board Summaries (Box 34)
  - National Voter (Box 34)
  - Binder of LWV materials (Box 35)
  - Convention packets (Box 35)
  - Monroe Co. - BCA (Box 35)
  - Conventions (Box 35)
  - Agendas, Minutes (Box 35)
  - Taxation and Schools (Box 35)
  - Program - Local - Schools (Box 35)
  - Local Gov't Finance (Box 35)
  - Schools (Box 35)
  - Memoranda (Box 36)
  - 1987 Program (Box 36)
  - Solid Waste Study (Box 36)
  - Re: PCBs (Box 36)
  - Solid Waste (Box 36)
  - Program (Box 36)
  - Index (Box 36)
  - Articles on EPA (Box 36)
  - Bloomington PCBs (Box 36)
  - Consent Decree (Box 36)
  - Correspondence from City of Bloomington (Box 36)
  - Environmental Action (Box 36)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 36)
  - Environmental Mediation (Box 36)
  - EPA Memos (Box 36)
  - EPA Public Relations (Box 36)
  - EPA Publications (Box 36)
  - Federal Legislation (Box 36)
  - General Electric (Box 36)
  - Hazardous Waste Management Articles (Box 36)
  - Hoosier Environmental Council (Box 36)
  - Household Hazardous Waste Programs (Box 36)
  - Incineration Information (Box 36)
  - Ind. Legislation (Box 36)
  - InPirg and Related Groups (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 36)
  - Municipal Solid Waste Management Articles (Box 36)
  - Correspondence from Westinghouse (Box 36)
  - Westinghouse Documents (Box 36)
  - Meetings (Box 36)
  - Local Work (Box 36)
  - Cerclis (Box 36)
  - West (Box 36)
  - Miscellaneous EPA Materials (Box 36)
  - Finance drives, 1961-1973 (Box 37)
    (12 folders)
  - Letters, highlights, 1974 (Box 37)
  - Finance drives, 1974-1984 (Box 37)
  - LWV records (binder) (Box 37)
  - Environment Assessment (Box 38)
  - Election Reporting, 1978 (Box 38)
  - "Keep to the Candidates" (Box 38)
  - Voter Service, 1963-1972 (Box 38)
  - Study of Indiana Election Laws (SIEL) (Box 38)
  - Pamphlets (Box 38)
  - Study of 20 Social Service Agencies, 1974-1976 (Box 38)
  - Health Care (Box 38)
  - Report (Box 38)
  - Samples of "Know Your Schools" (Box 39)
  - School Comm, 1974-1978 (Box 39)
  - School Transportation Study (Box 39)
  - Local Schools Consensus, 1972 (Box 39)
  - Consensus Materials, 1972 (Box 39)
  - Making Democracy Work (Box 39)
  - Program Planning (Box 39)
  - Taxes (Box 39)
  - VP Program (Box 39)
  - Who's Who - Indiana and National (Box 39)
  - Action Alert (Box 39)
  - Interest Sheets (Box 39)
  - Carol Wise (Box 39)
  - Stationary (Box 39)
  - Board Minutes (Box 39)
  - By-Laws (Box 39)
  - Ed Fund (Box 39)
  - Human Needs (Box 39)
  - Juvenile Criminals Con., 1996 (Box 39)
  - Leaders Handbook (Box 39)
  - Dedicated Funds (Box 39)
  - State Tax Structure (Box 39)
  - Speech for Public Meetings (Box 39)
  - Business Tax (Box 39)
  - Sales Tax (Box 39)
  - Know Your Schools (Box 40)
  - Ed Fund (Box 40)
  - International... (Box 40)
  - United Nations Study, 1976 (Box 40)
  - International Relations (Box 40)
  - Human Resources (Box 40)
  - Motor Vehicle License Branch (Box 40)
  - LWV records (binder) (Box 40)
  - Housing (Box 41)
  - Food and Nutrition (Box 41)
  - CAP and Rev Sharing (Box 41)
  - Food Stamps (Box 41)
  - Litigation (Box 41)
  - Migrant Workers (Box 41)
  - Human Rights Commission (Box 41)
  - Food Stamps (Box 41)
  - Welfare Reforms (Box 41)
  - Welfare Reform Coalition (Box 41)
  - Welfare - pamphlets and reports (Box 41)
  - Welfare (Box 41)
  - School desegregation (Box 41)
  - Health Care survey (Box 41)
  - Doctor's questionnaire (Box 41)
  - LWV records (Box 41)
  - Transportation and Trade (Box 42)
  - Schools/Education (Box 42)
  - "The Squeeze" - School Finance Project (binder) (Box 42)
  - Board Redistricting (Box 42)
  - Local School (Box 42)
  - Program - Local - Schools (Box 42)
  - School Issues (Box 42)
  - Current Interview Schedules and Letters (Box 42)
  - Clean Air Act (Box 42)
  - Cultural Arts Center (Box 42)
  - Public Lands (Box 42)
  - Natural Resources (Box 42)
  - EQCC Agenda (Box 42)
  - Oil and Gas Leasing (Box 42)
  - Clean Water (Box 42)
  - Coastal Zone Management (Box 42)
  - EQ/Land Use (Box 43)
  - Surface Mining Letters (Box 43)
  - Dept. of Natural Resources (Box 43)
  - Juvenile Justice (Box 43)
  - Program - Schools (Box 43)
  - Know Your School material (Box 43)
  - Mostly Finance (Box 43)
  - Year-Round School (Box 43)
  - School Students - Out-of-Pocket Expenses (Box 43)
  - Schools '73 Study (Box 43)
  - '73 Tabulation Survey (Box 43)
  - '74 Fact Sheet (Box 43)
  - '74 Finances (Box 43)
  - School Finance 1970 (Box 43)
  - City Plan Com. (Box 44)
  - Geologic Publications (Box 44)
  - Lake Monroe (Box 44)
  - U.S. Soil Conservation Office (Box 44)
  - Redevelopment (Box 44)
  - Lake Monroe (Box 44)
  - Regional Sewage Board (Box 44)
  - Energy (Box 44)
  - League Position and General Information (Box 44)
  - Air Travel (Box 44)
  - Alternative Fuels (Box 44)
  - Coal (Box 44)
  - Electricity (Box 44)
  - Energy and the Environment (Box 44)
  - Energy Education (Box 44)
  - Energy Fair 1981 (Box 44)
  - Home Appliances (Box 44)
  - Hydro Power (Box 44)
  - Nuclear Energy (Box 44)
  - Oil (Box 44)
  - Railroads (Box 44)
  - Recycling (Box 44)
  - Solar Energy (Box 44)
  - Transportation (Box 44)
  - Architecture (Box 44)
  - Wind Power (Box 44)
  - Important Forms (Box 44)
  - Sewage (Box 45)
  - Storm water (Box 45)
  - Burns Statute on Planning Conservation (Box 45)
  - New City Zoning Ordinance (Box 45)
  - Legislation City Co. Building Contracts between Govt's (Box 45)
  - Program - Streets and Roads (Box 45)
  - Streets, Roads and Thoroughfares (Box 45)
  - Sign Ordinance Hearings (Box 45)
  - Population (Box 45)
  - Program - National - 1975 (Box 45)
  - Program - State - Poor Relief Study (Box 45)
  - Taxes (Box 45)
  - Lake Lemo in Sedimentation (Box 45)
  - Environmental Quality Committee (Box 45)
  - City-County Coordination (Box 46)
  - Civil Rights (Box 46)
  - Constitutional Revision (Box 46)
  - Detention - Home Study (Box 46)
  - Health (Box 46)
  - Home Rule in Indiana (Box 46)
  - Hospital (Box 46)
  - Merit System (Box 46)
  - Milk (Box 46)
  - Rat Control (Box 46)
  - Reappointment (Box 46)
  - School Reorganization (Box 46)
  - Tax and Assessment (Box 46)
  - Urban Renewal (Box 46)
  - Voting Machine Levers (Box 46)
  - Local Water Problems (Box 46)
  - Sewer Tour Project (Box 46)
  - Finance (Box 47)
  - Legislature (Box 47)
  - Membership (Box 47)
  - Judicial (Box 47)
  - Membership (Box 47)
  - Judicial (Box 47)
  - Taxes (Box 47)
  - Welfare (Box 47)
  - National (Box 47)
  - Board List (Box 47)
  - By-Laws (Box 47)
  - Finance (Box 47)
  - Membership (Box 47)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 47)
  - Nominating Committee (Box 47)
  - Public Relations (Box 47)
  - Publications (Box 47)
  - Overseas Educ. Fund (Box 47)
  - Environmental Quality (Box 47)
  - ERA (Box 47)
  - Home Rule (Box 47)
  - Human Res. Employment (Box 47)
  - Water Resources (Box 47)
  - Loyalty/Security (Box 47)
  - Representative Government (Box 47)
  - Program - National - Urban Crisis - Consensus Questions (Box 47)
  - Human Resources - OEO - Welfare/Civil Rights (Box 47)
  - Human Resources - Housing and Education (Box 47)
  - Voter Service, 1973-1980 (Box 48)
  - Misc. Info (Box 48)
  - Officials List, 1981-1982 (Box 48)
  - Keys (Box 48)
  - Local Program Planning and Bylaws (Box 48)
  - Table of Contents (Box 48)
  - Prospective Lists (Box 48)
  - Calendar (Box 48)
  - List of Members (Box 48)
  - Local Program (Box 48)
  - State Program (Box 48)
  - Bylaws and Principles (Box 48)
  - History of LWVIN (Box 48)
  - League Program and You (Box 48)
  - Who Does What (Box 48)
  - Publications (Box 48)
  - Membership (Box 48)
  - Finance (Box 48)
  - How to Write Your Legislator (Box 48)
  - League Lingo (Box 48)
  - Official's List (Box 48)
  - U.S. LWM History - Pamphlet (Box 48)
  - National League Organization (binder) (Box 48)
  - Two plaques: Distinguished Service Award; Community Service Award (Box 49)
- Marge and Faber Files
  Scope and Contents
  Research files and local government documentation of Marge and Jim Faber, longtime members of the League and "Plan Committee," which monitored local government issues.
  - Environment (Box 49)
    - Hoosier National Forest - Off Road Vehicle use Areas, 1973 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Annual State of the Environment Report, 2001 (Box 50)
    - Wildlife Habitat, 1989 (Box 50)
  - Equal Rights Amendment (E.R.A.) (Box 50)
    - Bloomington - Pro-ERA Coalition, 1975-1976 (Box 50)
    - Hoosiers for the Equal Rights Amendment, 1975-1976 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Ratification - Legislature, 1976 (Box 50)
    - International Women's Year, 1975-1977 (Box 50)
    - LWVIN, 1975-1977 (Box 50)
    - LWVUS, 1974-1976 (Box 50)
    - Press Coverage, 1975-1976 (Box 50)
    - Publications - Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 50)
  - Lake Monroe (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe - Miscellaneous Resources, 1969-1986 (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe - Photos, Undated. (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe Land Suitability Study: A Technical Report, July 1975 (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe Land Suitability Study: A Technical Report - Maps, July 1975 (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe Land Suitability Study: Computer Program User's Manual, January 1976 (Box 50)
    - Lake Monroe Land Suitability Study: Executive Summary, July 1975 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - Correspondence and Public Statements, 1974-1980 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - History of Water in Monroe County (script), 1990 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - Local Government Committee, 1980 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - Local Government Committee - Fact Sheet, 1981 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - Local Government Committee - Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 50)
    - LWVBMC - Local Government Committee - Presentation to Monroe County Planning Commission, 8 February 1992 (Box 50)
    - LWVUS - Drinking Water Source Assessment and Protection, 1998 (Box 50)
    - Monroe Reservoir Theft, 2006 (Box 50)
  - Land Use (Box 50)
    - Bloomington Land Use Analysis, 1973 (Box 50)
    - "Farming on the Edge" (American Farmland Trust), 1997 (Box 50)
    - Flood Plain - Beanblossom Creek, 1974 (Box 50)
    - Flood Plain - Clear and Jackson Creeks, 1976 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Heartland Coordinating Commission - Report, 1974 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Land Resource Council - Report, 2000 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Land Use Issues (Purdue University Extension), 1975-2001 (Box 50)
    - Indiana Land Use on the Edge (Report), 1997 (Box 50)
    - Indiana's Erosion and Sedimentation Situation (Report), 1989 (Box 50)
    - Land Use - Miscellaneous Resources, 2000-2002 (Box 50)
    - Land Use Resources Catalog, November 2001 (Box 50)
    - League of Women Voters Materials (LWVUS, LWVBMC), 1974-1979 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County - Curry Pike Area TIF Transportation Study Update, 11 June 2001 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County - Curry Pike Area TIF Transportation Study Update, 29 August 2001 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County - Curry Pike Area TIF Transportation Study Update, 25 September 2001 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County - Tax Abatement Policy Review, 2000? (Box 50)
    - Monroe County Comprehensive Land Use Plan, 1996 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County Economic Development Commission - Minutes, September 2001 (Box 50)
    - Monroe County Redevelopment Commission - Minutes, July-August 2001 (Box 50)
    - Region 10 Planning Commission - Land Use Element, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Soil Survey of Monroe County, IN, 1981 (Box 50)
    - USDA Booklets, 1962-1972 (Box 50)
  - Local Government (Box 50)
    - CAP Facility Bonding, 1978 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study (2 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study (2 folders), 1976-1977 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study - Consensus Update, October 1977 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study - Cost Estimates, 1977 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study - Indiana Code, 1977 (Box 51)
    - City-County Building Study - Press Coverage), 1977 (Box 51)
    - City Reorganization (Plan Department, Community Development), 1974-1975 (Box 51)
    - LWVBMC - County Zoning Ordinance Review, 1979 (Box 51)
    - LWVBMC - Zoning Committee, 1968-1989 (Box 51)
    - Planning and Zoning, 1975-1977 (Box 51)
    - Planning and Zoning - County Zoning, 1977 (Box 51)
    - Townships - Indiana Code, Undated. (Box 51)
  - PCBs (Box 51)
    - Westinghouse Application and Responses, 1984-May 1986 (Box 51)
    - Westinghouse Information on O'Connor Combustor, 4 September 1986 (Box 51)
    - Clean-up Technologies, September 1986-1987 (Box 51)
    - Sludge Site Testing, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Sludge Site Testing, 1990 (Box 51)
    - Risk Assessment, 1991 (Box 51)
    - Ground Water, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Consent Decree, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Winston-Thomas Treatment Plant, 1995-1997 (Box 51)
    - Winston-Thomas Treatment Plant, December 1997 (Box 51)
    - Follow-up, 1998-1999 (Box 51)
    - Fell Iron and Fairview Elementary School, 1988-1989 (Box 51)
  - Planning (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - City Map, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Community Development - LWVBMC Recommendations, 1993 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Plan Commission - Hearings, April-July 1987 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Plan Commission - Hearings, August-September 1987 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Plan Commission - Hearings, October 1987 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Plan Commission - Hearings, March 1988 (Box 51)
    - Bloomington - Plan Commission - Hearings, December 1998-July 2002 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington - Proposed Annexation Maps, 1995 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington - Review of Master Plan, 1993 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington - Two-Mile Fringe Transfer to Monroe County, 1994-1995 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington - Zoning Ordinance (Title 20), 1985 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington - Zoning Ordinance - Annotated Outline, 26 July 1993 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington Environmental Quality Indicators, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Bloomington-Monroe County Parks and Recreation Department Master Plan, October 1986 (Box 52)
    - City of Bloomington Capital Improvement Plan, 1991-1995 (Box 52)
    - Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 52)
    - Communities at the Crossroads Conference, September 2005 (Box 52)
    - Community Development - "Building Better Communities", 2001 (Box 52)
    - Community Development - National Issues Forum, 17 November 2001 (Box 52)
    - Community Planning Handbook, 1979 (Box 52)
    - Concepts in Planning (LWV Casper, Wyoming), 1964 (Box 52)
    - Evaluating Your Zoning Ordinance (Purdue University), 1980 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Citizen Planners' Guide, Part 1: Plan Commission Basics, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Citizen Planners' Guide, Part 4: Communications, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Citizen Planners' Guide, Part 7: Comprehensive Plans, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Citizen Planners' Guide, Part 8: Zoning Ordinance, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Planning and Zoning Law (Indinaa Code 36-7-4), 1985-1986 (Box 52)
    - Indiana Planning and Zoning Laws, 1986 edition (Box 52)
    - LWVBMC - Suggested Comprehensive Planning Goals, 6 October 1988 (Box 52)
    - LWVBMC Sound Planning/Comprehensive Plan, 1987-1989 (Box 52)
    - LWVBMC Sound Planning/Comprehensive Plan, 1990-1993 (Box 52)
    - Manufactured Housing, 1977-1982 (Box 52)
    - Manufactured Housing Institute, 1985 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Board of Zoning Appeals - Minutes, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 8 June 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - LWVBMC Concerns about Draft 1, 9 June 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 24 July 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft with Comments, 4 August 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 31 August 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 25 October 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 23 November 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, 22 March 1994 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Comprehensive Land Use Plan - Draft, April 1995 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - "The County Master Plan" (Bloomington Monthly), January 1993 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Karst Inventory, July 2003 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Plan Commission - Minutes, 1994 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Plan Commission - Rules and Responsibilities, September 2003 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Plan Commission - Rules of Procedure, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Planning Department - Annual Work Summaries, 1986-1991 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Subdivision Control Ordinance, 2002 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Zoning Ordinance (Title 8), January 1987 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Zoning Ordinance (Title 8), Undated. (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Zoning Ordinance - Amendment, 16 March 1992 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County - Zoning Ordinance, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Monroe County and Zoning - Griffy Lake Development, 1988 (Box 53)
    - "Monroe County in Focus" (Bloomington Monthly), December 1990 (Box 53)
    - Monroe County Indiana 1985 Plat Book (Box 53)
    - Monroe County Maps, 1979-1994 (Box 53)
    - Monroe County Profile, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Monroe County: Quality of Our Environment, 1990 (Box 53)
    - Planning and Zoning - Indiana Code, 1985 (Box 53)
    - Stormwater Run-Off - Safflower Farms Subdivision, July-August 2003 (Box 53)
    - The Subdivision Impact Model: An Explanation and Validation (Purdue University), 1982 (Box 53)
    - Tax Abatement Policy, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Zoning Policies and Approaches for Bloomington, IN (City Council Review Draft), May 1993 (Box 53)
  - Roads (Box 53)
    - LWVBMC - Land Use Committee - State Road 37 Bypass Impact, Undated. (Box 53)
    - Monroe County Roads Study, 1976 (Box 53)
    - State Road 37 Conversion to Interstate Highway, 1992 (Box 53)
  - Solid Waste (Box 53)
    - Incineration and Ash Disposal (Environmental Defense Fund), 1982-1988 (Box 53)
    - Indiana Waste Management, 1988-1989 (Box 53)
    - LWVBMC - Solid Waste Committee, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Recycling, 1987-1990 (Box 53)